[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of car does Jake Ryan drive in the classic flick Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Porsche", "incorrect_answers": ["Rolls Royce", "69 Mustang", "Trans Am"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these authors created the famous fictional White Rabbit which wears a waistcoat and is always worried about being late?", "correct_answer": "Lewis Carrol", "incorrect_answers": ["J. R. R. Tolkien", "J. K. Rowling", "Edgar Allan Poe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of color is the shade called icterine?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Red", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was The Breakfast Club character Allison a nymphomaniac?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nowadays most animated movies are made using CGI. What does CGI stand  for?", "correct_answer": "Computer Generated Imagery", "incorrect_answers": ["Computer Generation I", "Computerized Generated Illusions", "Compensated Generic Images"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carbonyl chemical group in substances evokes the sensation of what taste?", "correct_answer": "Sweet", "incorrect_answers": ["Sour", "Chilly", "Bitter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular line by Jim Carreys character Ace Ventura does Morgan Freeman use in the 2003 comedy movie Bruce Almighty?", "correct_answer": "Alrighty then!", "incorrect_answers": ["Beautiful!", "Theres no place like home.", "Stay awake!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language adopted by the government of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Norwegian", "incorrect_answers": ["Norwegian and Finnish", "Norwegian and English", "Norwegian and Romani"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the Stayman convention in contract bridge?", "correct_answer": "George Rapee", "incorrect_answers": ["Samuel Stayman", "Bill Stayman", "George C. Stayman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what European country are the Rhine Falls located?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Austria", "Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the  suicidal uncle Frank in the movie Little Miss Sunshine?", "correct_answer": "Steve Carrell", "incorrect_answers": ["Lewis Black", "Steven Colbert", "Jon Stewart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What characteristics of the palm are explored by palm readers to predict the future or estimate the personality of its owner?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The fingers of the hand", "The lines of the skin", "The bumps of the skin"]}]